<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Assignment1</string>
    <string name="city_name">Seoul</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="home_cardview_text">
        * Country: South Korea\n
        * Area: Total	605.21 km2 (233.67 sq mi)\n
        * Population(2021): 9,765,869\n
        * Density: 16,000/km2 (42,000/sq mi)\n
        * Website: http://www.seoul.go.kr
    </string>
    <string name="food">Food</string>

    <string name="food_Hwangsaengga_name">Hwangsaengga</string>
    <string name="food_Hwangsaengga_description">Hwangsaengga Kalguksu specializes in Pyongyang-style kalguksu (hand-cut noodles). The star of the menu is sagol kalguksu, a hearty bowl of noodles in thick beef bone broth with pumpkin, mushrooms, and green onions for garnish; the subtle sweetness from the vegetables nicely mingles with the umami of the broth. In the summer, try the special kongguksu, noodles in cold broth made from ground soybeans, sesame, and various nuts. No matter the time of year, order a side of the soft, meaty dumplings for the table.</string>
    <string name="food_Hwangsaengga_address">78 Bukchon-ro 5-gil, Sogyeok-dong, Jongno-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="food_Wooraeok_name">Wooraeok</string>
    <string name="food_Wooraeok_description">Wooraeok has been serving delicious Korean barbecue in Seoul since 1946, but the restaurant is also well known for its Pyongyang naengmyeon (Pyongyang-style cold buckwheat noodles). While most versions of this dish feature a subtle broth — often derided as bland — Wooraeok’s version is meatier and more flavorful, making it suitable for first-timers.</string>
    <string name="food_Wooraeok_address">62–29 Changgyeonggung-ro, Jung-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="food_TukTukNoodleThai_name">Tuk Tuk Noodle Thai</string>
    <string name="food_TukTukNoodleThai_description">Among Yeonnam-dong’s vibrant streets you’ll find Tuk Tuk Noodle Thai, where Thai chefs have served the area for over a decade. The interior is decorated with items that owner Im Donghyuk and the team brought from Thailand. Try a handful of dishes and chase them down with ice-cold Thai beers, or something from the selection of Champagne and natural wines. Sister restaurant Soi Yeonnam Mao in Gangnam is another excellent option with a smaller menu featuring Tuk Tuk’s greatest hits.</string>
    <string name="food_TukTukNoodleThai_address">161–8 Seongmisan-ro, Mapo-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="food_CharlesH_name">Charles H</string>
    <string name="food_CharlesH_description">Named the best bar in Korea on the Asia’s 50 Best Bars list in 2022, Charles H is a speakeasy discreetly hidden away in the lower level of the Four Seasons Hotel Seoul. After passing through a secret passage, guests find a glamorous interior suited for a lux hotel bar with decor inspired by Korea’s traditional metal ornaments. The cocktail list contains classics and original creations inspired by Charles H. Baker, the eponymous bon vivant who wrote the classic cocktail book The Gentleman’s Companion.</string>
    <string name="food_CharlesH_address">97 Saemunan-ro, Jongno-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="food_BarCham_name">Bar Cham</string>
    <string name="food_BarCham_description">Wind your way through the alleys of Seochon until you come across the unassuming hanoak (traditional Korean house) that houses Bar Cham. There, award-winning bartender Lim Byung-jin serves uniquely Korean signature cocktails, each named for the region that produced the local spirit featured in the drink. The interior, which goes hard on oak (or “cham” in Korean), is cozy and relaxing. Bar Cham made the 2022 Asia’s 50 Best Bars list, and there are various non-alcoholic cocktail options just as delicious as their alcoholic counterparts.</string>
    <string name="food_BarCham_address">34 Jahamun-ro 7-gil, Tongin-dong, Jongno-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="food_Kojima_name">Kojima</string>
    <string name="food_Kojima_description">With access to fresh seafood and the rich cultural influence of Japan, Seoul is home to some of the finest sushi outside of Japan. There are options at all price points, from cheap lunch boxes to high-end sushi, but many cite Kojima as the best in Korea. Located on top of luxury clothing store Boon the Shop, the restaurant is led by chef Kyung Jae Park, one of Seoul’s most respected sushi veterans, who gained a following while training at the Shilla Hotel’s Ariake and then cemented his reputation at his first restaurant, Sushi Chohi.</string>
    <string name="food_Kojima_address">21 Apgujeong-ro 60-gil, Gangnam-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="food_BawiPastaBar_name">Bawi Pasta Bar</string>
    <string name="food_BawiPastaBar_description">Fresh pasta is having a moment in Korea, and Bawi Pasta Bar is at the center of the trend. Chef Kim Hyun-Joong started the business as a one-man operation in a deserted alley, pressing dough into noodles to order. His early hit, mint pistachio pesto, has become a cult favorite, along with others like squid ink pasta topped with caviar. Although Bawi has relocated to a newer, bigger venue, Kim still cooks alone for the most part for the eight-seat counter, and much of his 10-course dinners unfold in front of guests’ eyes. The calm black interior and excellent playlist add a zen-like ambiance that wouldn’t be out of place at a high-end Japanese restaurant. Reservations through Catchtable, a local reservation app, are a must — though very hard to come by.</string>
    <string name="food_BawiPastaBar_address">254 Itaewon-ro, Yongsan-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="food_MaisonJo_name">Maison Jo</string>
    <string name="food_MaisonJo_description">Chef Jo Woo-Ram worked for five years at Maison Verot, a famous charcuterie restaurant in Paris, before opening ​​Maison Jo, Seoul’s leading French charcuterie house. The takeout menu of high-quality charcuteries includes pate, terrine, and saucisson, all made from Korean ingredients, as well as baguettes and other French breads and pastries made by patissier Lee Eunhee. Maison Jo’s jambon-beurre — a generous amount of butter and jambon blanc stuffed between slices of housemade baguette — is one of the city’s best sandwiches. You can also pick up premium European groceries such as olive oil, vinegar, and various natural wines.</string>
    <string name="food_MaisonJo_address">35 Banpo-daero 7-gil, Seocho 3(sam)-dong, Seocho-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>

    <string name="food_CoffeeLibre_name">Coffee Libre</string>
    <string name="food_CoffeeLibre_description">For over a decade, Coffee Libre has pioneered the specialty coffee market in Korea. These days, the operation buys beans directly from over 100 farms in 12 countries, roasts them in Korea, and supplies more than 400 cafes in the country. Beyond supplying others, the brand has four of its own stores, including the main location in Yeonnam. Coffee Libre’s latte, made with an acidic double shot of espresso and warm milk, has become the standard for specialty coffee shops in Korea.</string>
    <string name="food_CoffeeLibre_address">198 Seongmisan-ro, Yeonnam-dong, Mapo-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="food_FritzCoffeeCompany_name">Fritz Coffee Company</string>
    <string name="food_FritzCoffeeCompany_description">Award-winning baristas, a dedicated buyer for green coffee beans, and a famed baker joined forces to start Fritz Coffee Company, which is seated in a beautiful old space that was once a Korean barbecue restaurant. The coffee powerhouse imports beans directly from producers around the world and roasts them in-house. The bread and pastries, freshly baked every morning by famed baker Minsu Heo, are the pairing that Seoul’s best cup of coffee deserves.</string>
    <string name="food_FritzCoffeeCompany_address">17 Saechang-ro 2-gil, Dohwa-dong, Mapo-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="food_TartineBakeryDosan_name">Tartine Bakery Dosan</string>
    <string name="food_TartineBakeryDosan_description">Chad Robertson’s San Francisco icon, Tartine Bakery, chose Seoul as its second home, opening its first global outpost in 2018; the city now has six locations. The Dosan branch shares space with Kinfolk Lounge, the independent lifestyle magazine’s first physical space, in a two-story glass-walled building that boasts a beautiful seating area with a courtyard and a terrace. Enjoy Tartine classics such as sourdough and banana cream pie with specialty coffee while reading a Kinfolk magazine. The space also hosts various pop-ups and exhibitions, so check out the website for current events.</string>
    <string name="food_TartineBakeryDosan_address">24 Eonju-ro 168-gil, Apgujeong-dong, Gangnam-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="food_MaisonMO_name">Maison M\'O</string>
    <string name="food_MaisonMO_description">Korea’s leading French dessert shop is operated by husband and wife patissier duo Otsuka Tetsuya and Min-sun Lee. The two met at Pierre Herme Paris in Tokyo, where Tetsuya served as executive chef and Lee as pastry chef. Using techniques accumulated in France and Japan, the two patissiers offer more than 50 high-quality desserts both classic and innovative, including pastries, cookies, and cakes. Maison M’O is often credited for popularizing madeleines in Korea, offering them in flavors like lemon, salted chocolate, and chestnut. If you can’t make it to the patisserie in Bangbae-dong, pick up some sweets online or at Blue Bottle Coffee locations across Korea.</string>
    <string name="food_MaisonMO_address">22 Bangbae-ro 26-gil, Seocho-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="food_OldFerryDonut_name">Old Ferry Donut</string>
    <string name="food_OldFerryDonut_description">Old Ferry Donut is a donut specialty shop that introduced yeast donuts(using a dough that went through over 12 hours of low-temperature fermentation) to Korea for the first time. CEO Choi Min-yi had traveled across the United States looking for great donuts after getting inspired by the texture and flavor of the donut she had in New York. She created a donut brand presenting flavors that could appeal to the Korean palette and the product packaging with Korean folk paintings(‘Hojakdo’ depicting tiger, magpie and pine tree) on it. </string>
    <string name="food_OldFerryDonut_address">66 Hannam-daero 27-gil, Yongsan-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="food_PontCafe_name">Pont Cafe</string>
    <string name="food_PontCafe_description">Pont Cafe Seoul is an old railway office that has been transformed into a coffee shop in the city’s Yongsan District. The space is bright and minimalistic, with Scandinavian-style furnishings. Many of the materials that have been used to renovate the space are the same that would have been used to create the former 1940s railway office. For instance, bricks, metal, and wood. In many ways, this helps to retain the feel of the cafe’s original purpose. Pont is a coffee roastery, and it prides itself on its single-origin filtered coffee. You will find a wide range of sweet and savoury snacks on the menu - from cheese scones to chocolate brownies.</string>
    <string name="food_PontCafe_address">19–16 Hangang-daero 15-gil, Yongsan-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>

    <string name="food_BigLights_name">Big Lights</string>
    <string name="food_BigLights_description">Seoul’s first natural wine bar, Big Lights, played a significant role in today’s natural wine craze in Korea. The wine bar opened in 2017 as a semi-private bar that only took reservations through referrals — thankfully, that’s not the case anymore. Its new location functions as part of the showroom for Danish furniture brand Fritz Hansen, with furniture and lighting by the retailer. The wine list lives up to the hype, and the food cooked using wood fire is also top-notch. Keep an eye on their Instagram for occasional wine tastings, when rare wines are sometimes sold by the glass at reasonable prices.</string>
    <string name="food_BigLights_address">61–17 Hannam-daero 20-gil, Yongsan-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="food_BarMusk_name">Bar Musk</string>
    <string name="food_BarMusk_description">\'Quiet Please! Whisky Sleeping\', reads the golden-liveried sign on the door leading to Bar Musk. Setting a tone of serious and contemplative drinking, this Seoul bar has been designed to create a luxurious and peaceful cocktail experience. In a long, wood-dominating venue, with nods to an almost church-like architecture (think vaulted ceiling and pillars), its cosy and deeply relaxing. Like being inside a whisky barrel. If guests are after more than neat drams, the mixed drinks here focus on highballs and classic serves, executed meticulously and with reverence to the spirit and ice.</string>
    <string name="food_BarMusk_address">14 Eonju-ro 152-gil, Gangnam-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="food_BarTeaScent_name">Bar Tea Scent</string>
    <string name="food_BarTeaScent_description">There’s one undisputed hero at this tea-room themed cocktail bar, and that’s the tea itself. Prepare yourself to be immersed in all things tea in a stylish setting with minimalist decor, accompanied by gentle music and the sounds of water. For the full experience, there’s a five-course Tea Omakase, starting with ceremonial matcha and ending with lapsang souchong-infused scotch. Or dive into the bar’s list of signature tea cocktails, each of which can be made with or without alcohol. There’s a selection of tea-infused spirits available by the glass or bottle, and a choice of rare single-origin teas too. A pair of tea-infused bar-food options round out this tribute to camellia sinensis.</string>
    <string name="food_BarTeaScent_address">83–12 Cheongdam-dong, Gangnam-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="food_MinersBar_name">Miners Bar</string>
    <string name="food_MinersBar_description">Miners is a fun and friendly local joint, with an equally approachable cocktail programme. The ‘Berry Backhoe’ is a blend of lemongrass vodka, berries, orange flower water, passion fruit syrup, lemon and ginger beer, while the ‘Geared Pastry’ mixes vodka, Pedro Ximénez sherry, coffee rum, falernum, espresso and Angostura bitters. The vibe here is chilled out, with exposed brick walls. This is basically the bar that everybody wishes they had in their neighbourhood.</string>
    <string name="food_MinersBar_address">31 Hannam-daero 21-gil, Hannam-dong, Yongsan-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="food_MarquedAmour_name">Marque d\'Amour</string>
    <string name="food_MarquedAmour_description">The top floor of Seoul’s L’Escape Hotel – the design of which evokes 19th Century France – contains an opulent cocktail space with some big names behind it. Set up by global bartending legends Simone Caporale, Monica Berg and Alex Kratena, Marque D\'amour combines the hotel’s French design cues with local Korean ones, resulting in an intimate, lush environment complete with peacock sculptures and no shortage of gold, velvet and wood panelling. Flowers and plants are the focus of the bar’s signature drinks, with inventive presentation for each. Don’t miss the Rainbow G&amp;T, served with layers of citrus fruit.</string>
    <string name="food_MarquedAmour_address">67 Toegye-ro, Jung-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="food_LeChamber_name">Le Chamber</string>
    <string name="food_LeChamber_description">Access to sumptuous speakeasy Le Chamber depends on pulling the correct book from the bookshelf entrance: a much-Instagrammed touch dreamed up by world-champion bartender-owners Eom Do-hwan and Lim Jae-jin. With a 50-guest capacity, the space features high ceilings, leather seating, glittering chandeliers and live piano music. Menus, presented in hardcover books, boast some 200 whiskies, house-made ingredients, including ginger beer, and fermented pours. With a bottle-storage facility for VIPs, don’t be surprised if you spot a K-pop star sipping a Gatsby-style cocktail, complete with a picture of Leonardo DiCaprio clipped to the glass.</string>
    <string name="food_LeChamber_address">42 Dosan-daero 55-gil, Cheongdam-dong, Gangnam-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="entertainment">Entertainment</string>
    <string name="entertainment_LotteWorld_name">Lotte World</string>
    <string name="entertainment_LotteWorld_description">Lotte World is the largest theme park in Seoul that has both indoor and outdoor theme parks. It’s connected to Jamsil Station, where you can stop by various attractions including Lotte World Tower, Lotte World Aquarium, Lotte World Mall, and Seokchon Lake Park. With Magic Pass Premium, you can skip the lines for 3 or 5 popular attractions, which can massively save your time! Lotte World opened its second location in Busan recently as well.</string>
    <string name="entertainment_LotteWorld_address">240 Olympic-ro, Songpa-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="entertainment_Everland_name">Everland</string>
    <string name="entertainment_Everland_description">Everland is Korea’s largest theme park that is famous for having a variety of attractions and rides, such as the T-Express wooden roller coaster and Lost Valley where you can have an up-close and in-person interaction with animals. It’s located in Yongin, Gyeonggi-do and you can easily reach from Seoul by subway or shuttle bus.</string>
    <string name="entertainment_Everland_address">199 Everland-ro, Pogog-eup, Cheoin-gu, Yongin-si, Gyeonggi-do, South Korea</string>
    <string name="entertainment_SeoulChildrensGrandPark_name">Seoul Children’s Grand Park</string>
    <string name="entertainment_SeoulChildrensGrandPark_description">Situated in Seoul’s Gwangjin-gu, Children’s Grand Park offers a zoo, botanical garden, amusement facilities, and diverse performance events for children and families. It was opened on a Korean public holiday called Children’s Day (May 5th), which is a day for children just like its name. The entrance fee is free of charge but you have to pay for each ride at the theme park (Adult – 5,000 Won / Teenagers – 4,000 Won / Children 3,500 Won). If you have kids, this theme park is definitely a must-visit!</string>
    <string name="entertainment_SeoulChildrensGrandPark_address">216 Neungdong-ro, Gwangjin-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="entertainment_SeoulForestPark_name">Seoul Forest Park</string>
    <string name="entertainment_SeoulForestPark_description">Inspired by New York’s Central Park, Seoul Forest offers a plethora of things to do. The Ecological Forest is a protected natural habitat that’s home to animals including deer, chipmunks and ducks. At the Nature Study Field, previously a water-treatment facility, you’ll find beautiful wildflower plantings and a botanical garden. The centerpiece of the forest, the Culture and Art Park offers decorative flower beds and performances on an outdoor stage. With greenhouses filled with butterflies, deer to feed, bikes to rent and grassy fields that are surrounded by cherry blossoms in the spring and vibrant foliage in fall, Seoul Forest offers endless options for a romantic afternoon.</string>
    <string name="entertainment_SeoulForestPark_address">273 Ttukseom-ro, Seongdong-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="entertainment_WorldCupPark_name">World Cup Park</string>
    <string name="entertainment_WorldCupPark_description">World Cup Park encompasses five different parks, of which Haneul Park the best known. On the top of a hillside, Haneul Park has beautiful eulalia grass that is lush and green throughout summer and turns golden in the fall, when crowds descend on the area to look out at the amazing views out over the city as the grass waves in the wind in the foreground. Don’t miss out on the other four parks: Nanji Stream Park, Nanji Han River Park, Sunset Park and Peace Park have an amazing array of plants, including metasequoia trees, cherry trees, pink muhly, cosmos flowers and more. Sunset Park has campgrounds and a nine-hole golf course while Peace Park features artistic installations left over from gardening expos. Nanji Stream Park and Nanji Han River Park have sports fields, a skate park and bike rental facilities. World Cup Park is a lovely place to spend a day – or several days.</string>
    <string name="entertainment_WorldCupPark_address">243–60 Woldeukeom-ro, Mapo-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="entertainment_NaksanPark_name">Naksan Park</string>
    <string name="entertainment_NaksanPark_description">Conveniently located in downtown Seoul near the popular shopping district of Dongdaemun, Naksan Park occupies the side of a mountain and offers stunning views out over the city. While a visit here requires a walk uphill, the spectacular views of the city at the top make every step worth it. As you follow along a portion of the old Seoul Fortress Wall on the way up, you’ll contemplate the city’s history while looking out onto the modern metropolis beyond. The park also has beautiful gardens with flowers in bloom every spring and summer. From the Hyehwa subway station, most park visitors stop to rest and enjoy the views in the park en route to the nearby Ihwa Mural Village. This photogenic place was lovingly decorated with murals by 70 artists in 2006 in an effort to revitalize the neighborhood; today, it’s a marvelous neighborhood filled with cute cafes.</string>
    <string name="entertainment_NaksanPark_address">41 Naksan-gil, Jongno-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="entertainment_Deoksugung_name">Deoksugung</string>
    <string name="entertainment_Deoksugung_description">Deoksugung Palace is a fabulous Korean palace in having a modern seal engraving and a garden and fountain in western style. In Deoksugung Palace, medieval and modern style architecture resides in harmony. You will find the Royal Guards outside this palace conducting their turn over ceremonies, and a visit to this palace is the essential things to do in Seoul. The Deoksugung Palace was the home of Prince Wolsan, King Seongjong\'s older brother. The residence had not yet been known as a palace at that time. The area consisted of residential buildings for royal family descendants. In 1592, During the Japanese occupation of Korea, the residential buildings became a provisional royal residence after fires had destroyed all the other palaces. It became the palace's main entrance after the Wongudan Altar (Hwangudan Altar) was completed. Inhwamun has initially been the main gate. It was shifted to the west in 1970 due to Taepyeong-no Street's nearby development.</string>
    <string name="entertainment_Deoksugung_address">99 Sejong-daero, Jung-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="entertainment_Changgyeonggung_name">Changgyeonggung</string>
    <string name="entertainment_Changgyeonggung_description">Changgyeonggung Palace was used as a royal residence and as a secondary palace for queens and the King\'s son. Changgyeonggung Palace lies in the heart of Seoul. In 1104, during the reign of King Sukjong of the Goryeo Dynasty, a summer palace known as Sunganggung was first constructed there. In 1392, at the start of the Joseon Dynasty, Korea\'s capital was relocated from Kaesong, now North Korea, to Seoul, then known as Hanyang. King Sejong built a new royal residence at this site in 1418 for his father, King Taejong. King Seongjong expanded the palace buildings for King Sejo\'s widows in the year 1483 and 1484. At that time, the royal residence was called Changgyeonggung Palace. Changgyeonggung was known as Changgyeonggungwon (Changgyeong Garden) during the Japanese occupation of Korea from the year 1910–1945. It was converted from a luxurious royal palace into a hotel with a zoo and botanical garden. Changgyeonggung Palace, together with Changdeokgung Palace, is known as Donggwol, or the East Palace is a must thing to do in Seoul</string>
    <string name="entertainment_Changgyeonggung_address">185 Changgyeonggung-ro, Jongno-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="entertainment_Changdeokgung_name">Changdeokgung</string>
    <string name="entertainment_Changdeokgung_description">Changdeokgung Palace is located to the east of Gyeongbokgung Palace, and it is also known as Donggwol, the Eastern Palace. The castle has been home to the government of Joseon for 270 years and was also the favorite residence of many kings of the Joseon Dynasty. The Changdeokgung Palace is the royal residential palace with the most extended service. Changdeokgung Palace is well-preserved relative to other castles and still has many of its original features. The way the buildings blend into the surrounding landscape is a specific quality of Changdeokgung Palace. The back garden of the palace, Huwon, is considered an exceptional example of a Korean garden layout and is the only rear garden of any Korean palace. Changdeokgung Palace was renowned as the World Heritage List of UNESCO in the year 1997, and it’s a must-visit place and things to do in Seoul. Huwon is self-contained and occupies 60% of Changdeokgung. The buildings of the palace are situated on the hill of Bugaksan (Mt.) and have very few artificial features to blend with their natural environment. A large lake, Buyongji, together with Buyongjeong (Pavilion) and Juhapru (Pavilion), is situated in the center of Huwon. A cross-shaped roof and two supporting pillars from the pond make Buyongjeong\'s design unique. King Jeongjo (the Joseon Dynasty's twenty-second king) and his courtiers are said to have sometimes enjoyed fishing here in Buyongjeong.</string>
    <string name="entertainment_Changdeokgung_address">Gwonnong-dong, Jongno-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="entertainment_Gwanghwamun_name">Gwanghwamun</string>
    <string name="entertainment_Gwanghwamun_description">Gwanghwamun Gate is the Gyeongbokgung Palace\'s formidable main gate. Over the years, the entrance has been redesigned several times but remains an emblem of Seoul. Construction started at the beginning of the Joseon dynasty in the year 1395. The gate soon became one of the Joseon Dynasty\'s most essential barriers as it protected the main palace. Three other gates are located along the walls surrounding the castle at 2,404 meters (7,887 feet). Sinmumun, Geonchunmun, and Yeongchumun are the other three gates. The gate is made up of three entrances and a tall pavilion of two stories. Several watchtowers once guarded Gwanghwamun. Upon their occupation of Korea during the Imjin War in 1592, the gate was demolished by the Japanese. In 1867, almost 250 years later, during the reconstruction of nearby Gyeongbokgung Palace, the gate was restored. During the Korean War, the wooden gatehouse of Gwanghwamun Gate was again demolished. Work started to restore Gwanghwamun to its original wooden specifications in December 2006. Historical details were given special attention to the restoration work. Restoration work got completed on August 15, 2010, at the cost of winning 28 billion.</string>
    <string name="entertainment_Gwanghwamun_address">12 Hyoja-ro, Jongno-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="entertainment_Gyeongbokgung_name">Gyeongbokgung</string>
    <string name="entertainment_Gyeongbokgung_description">The Palace of Gyeongbokgung was the first and largest royal palace built during the Joseon Dynasty. Completed in the year 1395, Gyeongbokgung Palace was located in the heart of Seoul\'s newly established capital (then known as Hanyang) and represented the Joseon Dynasty\'s sovereignty. Gyeongbokgung, the largest of the Five Grand Palaces (the others being Gyeonghuigung Palace, Deoksugung Palace, Changgyeonggung Palace, Changdeokgung Palace), served as the Joseon Dynasty\'s main palace. The government of Korea has spent a great deal of time and effort to repair, preserve, and retain the castle for future generations. Such projects include work on improving and restoring the structures that were lost during the invasion of Japan. Tourists can visit Korea\'s National Palace Museum and Korea's National Folk Museum; must-visit things to do in Seoul as they are on the Gyeongbokgung palace grounds. In December 2018, the western gate of the palace, Yeongchumun, was opened to the public to enhance connectivity from Gyeongbokgung Palace to Seochon and vice versa. There have been only three entrances to Gyeongbokgung Palace for the past 43 years-Gwanghwamun's southern gate, Sinmumun's northern gate, and Korea's National Folk Museum's eastern entrance.</string>
    <string name="entertainment_Gyeongbokgung_address">161 Sajik-ro, Jongno-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="entertainment_BukchonHanokVillage_name">Bukchon Hanok Village</string>
    <string name="entertainment_BukchonHanokVillage_description">Bukchon Hanok Village is a historic village featuring hanok or traditional Korean dwellings from the Joseon Dynasty, which dates back nearly 600 years. Bukchon means "northern village." The quaint residential town is located in a hilly area north of Cheonggyecheon Stream and between two royal palaces, Gyeongbokgung Palace and Changdeokgung Palace. A hanok is a traditional wooden house found throughout Korea at one time. The new concrete structures have replaced the old-style buildings. During the Joseon Dynasty, royal families, aristocrats, wealthy citizens, and government officials lived in many of the village\'s hanok residences. While many other areas in Seoul are filled with high elevations and new buildings, the Bukchon Hanok Village has remained remarkably intact with mostly low elevation buildings. There are around 900 hanok buildings in the city, many of which have been restored to their former glory using traditional designs and materials. Today, Bukchon Hanok Village is a beautiful array of restaurants, tea houses, cultural centers, and more.</string>
    <string name="entertainment_BukchonHanokVillage_address">37, Gyedong-gil, Jongno-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="entertainment_Myeongdong_name">Myeong-dong</string>
    <string name="entertainment_Myeongdong_description">Myeong-dong is the place to go if you’re planning to hit the shops during your stay in the capital. One of South Korea’s prime shopping districts, it has dozens of department stores, shopping malls, and street-side shops. Popular items include inexpensive clothes, shoes, accessories, jewellery, and handbags from local and international brands. There are over 1,000 outlets selling Korean cosmetics and skincare. Myeongdong Market also has sightseeing spots – iconic landmarks include the Myeongdong Catholic Cathedral and Myeongdong Nanta Theatre.</string>
    <string name="entertainment_Myeongdong_address">Myeong-dong, Jung-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="entertainment_Dongdaemun_name">Dongdaemun</string>
    <string name="entertainment_Dongdaemun_description">Dongdaemun is one of South Korea’s largest wholesale and retail shopping districts. It has around 26 shopping malls, 30,000 speciality shops, and 50,000 manufacturers. Items range from textiles, clothes, shoes, and jewellery, to leather goods, toys, electronics, and office supplies. Dongdaemun attracts foodies with Mukja Golmok, an alley dedicated to Korean street food and snacks. The shopping district stays busy well into the night, with festivities, fashion shows, music and dance performances taking place after the sun sets in Seoul. </string>
    <string name="entertainment_Dongdaemun_address">Euljiro 6(yuk)-ga, Jung-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="entertainment_Hongdae_name">Hongdae</string>
    <string name="entertainment_Hongdae_description">Hongdae is known for its youthful ambience, underground cultures, and freedom of self-expression. Local youths and students of the neighbouring Hongik University often visit the district’s many cafes, art galleries, fashion outlets, live music bars and clubs. There are plenty of shops selling goods ranging from handmade clothes to luxury goods. Hongdae\'s main draw is its weekend ‘free market, which takes place from 1pm to 6pm. Local artists and craftsmen showcase their handmade crafts, accessories, paintings, and second-hand goods. You can also catch live dance performances, literary exhibits, cultural events, street performances, and festivals.</string>
    <string name="entertainment_Hongdae_address">364–27 Seogyo-dong, Mapo-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="transportation">Transportation</string>
    <string name="nametextview">nameTextview</string>
    <string name="categorytextview">categoryTextview</string>
    <string name="districttextview">districtTextview</string>
    <string name="latitude">Latitude</string>
    <string name="longitude">Longitude</string>
    <string name="reset_marker">Reset Center to My Location</string>
    <string name="google_map">Open my location</string>
    <string name="bus">Bus</string>
    <string name="subway">Subway</string>
    <string name="taxi">Taxi</string>
    <string name="bus_title1">Regional Buses</string>
    <string name="bus_content1">
        # Yellow Bus : 1st number (Area where bus is operating) / 2nd number (serial number (1~))\n
        # Blue Bus : 2nd number (Departure area) / 2nd number (Arrival area) / 3rd number (serial number (0~))\n
        # Green Bus : 1st number (Departure area) / 2nd number (Arrival area) / 3rd number (serial number (11~))\n
        # Red Bus : : 1st number (9) / 2nd number (Departure area) / 3rd number (serial number (00~))\n
        # Customized Bus : 1st number (8) / 2nd number (Departure area) / 3rd number (Arrival area) / 4th number (serial number (0~))\n
        # Airport Bus : 1st number (6 (0~7)) / Third Number (serial number (00~))\n
        # Midnight Bus : 1st number (N) / 2nd number (Departure area) / 3rd number (Arrival area)
    </string>

    <string name="bus_title2">Seoul Bus Numbers</string>
    <string name="bus_content2">
        # 0 area (Major Districts : Jung-gu, Jongno-gu, Yongsan-gu / Extension Line : none)\n
        # 1st area (Major Districts : Seongbuk-gu, Gangbuk-gu, Dobong-gu, Nowon-gu / Extension Line : Gyeonggi-do Yangju-si, Uijeongbu-si, Dongducheon-si, Pocheon-si)\n
        # 2nd area (Major Districts : Seongdong-gu, Gwangjin-gu, Dongdaemun-gu, Jungnang-gu / Extension Line : Gyeonggi-do Guri-si, Namyangju-si, Gapyeong-gun, Yangpyeong-gun)\n
        # 3rd area (Major Districts : Songpa-gu, Gangdong-gu / Extension Line : Gyeonggi-do Gwangju-si, Hanam-si, Icheon-si, Yeoju-si)\n
        # 4th area (Major Districts :Seocho-gu, Gangnam-gu / Extension Line : Gyeonggi-do Seongnam-si, Yongin-si, Anseong-si)\n
        # 5th area (Major Districts : Geumcheon-gu, Dongjak-gu, Gwanak-gu / Extension Line : Gyeonggi-do Anyang-si, Gunpo-si, Uiwang-si, Ansan-si, Gwacheon-si, Suwon-si, Hwaseong-si, Osan-si, Pyeongtaek-si)\n
        # 6th area (Major Districts : Yangcheon-gu, Gangseo-gu, Guro-gu, Yeongdeungpo-gu / Extension Line : Incheon Metropolitan City, Gyeonggi-do Gimpo-si, Bucheon-si, Gwangmyeong-si, Siheung-si)\n
        # 7th area (Major Districts : Eunpyeong-gu, Seodaemun-gu, Mapo-gu / Extension Line : Gyeonggi-do  Goyang-si, Paju-si, Yeoncheon-gun)
    </string>

    <string name="bus_title3">Fare &amp; Transfer System</string>
    <string name="bus_content3">
        # Fares can be paid with cash or transportation card for a flat rate each time you board\n
        # Fares for Seoul city buses and Maeul (Village) buses can be paid with T-money, U-Pass, EB Card, Cashbee, and Korail Membership Cards. Deferred payment transportation cards, which are compatible with T-Money and U-Pass, can be used as well.\n
        # Seoul city buses are free for a maximum of 3 children under the age of 6 if they are accompanied by a guardian. Legal free riders who are defined in the Passenger Transport Service Act of Korea are also able to ride for free.\n
        # Seoul, Gyeonggi Province (Gyeonggi-do), Incheon buses and metropolitan subways are under the Metropolitan Integrated Fare System, so they charge a basic fare for distances up to 10 km. Using Seoul metropolitan buses, Gyeonggi Province general buses, non-stop deluxe buses, Incheon buses, and red buses for no more than one transfer will cost the basic fare up to 30 km, and an extra KRW 100 for each additional 5 km (for adults).\n
        # Multiple passengers on one card and transfer discounts are available only on city buses, and only if those passengers are traveling to the same destination.
    </string>

    <string name="bus_title4">T-money Card</string>
    <string name="bus_content4">
        # T-money is a transport card issued by Korea Smart Card. It can be used as a transport card and e-currency. It is commonly used in the metropolitan area, along with Cashbee.\n
        # T-money transport cards come in two types: a common T-money card and a Smart T-money card. Smart T-money cards are sold in various forms, such as key rings and cell phone rings. All T-money cards can be recharged at subway stations and convenience stores.
    </string>


    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>